# **DON EDDY**

(209) 712-7638 | da.eddy@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/daeddy/

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

# CONTRACT Front-End Web Developer

Front-end Web Developer with a focus on user interfaces using programming languages: HTML, CSS and JavaScript to design a quality user experience and advanced user interface with cross-browser compatibility. Familiar with contemporary front-end JavaScript frameworks like Vue.js. 10+ years professional and freelance experience. Applying for Contract Front-end Web Developer position.

### SKILLS

- Software: Visual Studio Code, Git Bash(version control tools, Windows, Apple, Linux command-line, Asana, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Chrome and Firefox and Safari debugging tools
- Languages: JavaScript (ES5/6+), CSS/SASS, HTML, Twig, PHP, MySQL
- Frameworks/CMS: Drupal 6-8, WordPress, Vue.js, GraphQL, JAMstack, Gridsome
- Other: OOP, Git, Node.js/NPM, CSS Grid, Docker, Lando

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

The Novel Tech, Stockton, CA 08/2016 - Present

#### **Lighting Director**

- Cooperate with clients and interpret needs of stakeholders and business leaders.
- Direct crew of one to twelve to construct lighting for large corporate meetings.
- Met Highly technical requirements with non-technical communication with competitive estimates accomplishing their visual design.

Robinsons Feed Co., Lodi, CA 07/2006- 04/2016

#### IT Director

- Implemented Asana project tracking software for staff to simplify company communications to help managers collaborate across four locations and eliminated lost valuable customer interaction time.
- Independantly programmed and completed custom Drupal user interface for intranet special order web application bringing their business onto the Zen Server application architecture, improving user experience for employees.
- Created the visual design with user feedback and research on Ux Design and themed company-first web application.
- Provided user support to employer and staff on emerging technologies and changes to data and application infrastructure where antiquated technical training existed.

iSelect Internet, Lodi, CA 05/2008 - 07/2011

## Web Developer / Programmer

- Research new clients web site needs, create estimates for desired user experience and help with technical issues.
- Fashioned graphic mockups with Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Design cross-browser compatible Front-end user interfaces cooperatively with clients, theming Drupal, Wordpress and custom CMS.
- Use of tools such as Git version control tools, increasing productivity.
- Developing and programming semantic HTML, CSS and JavaScript, building sites using current web best practices.

## **EDUCATION**

**Diploma for Master of Recording II Program, 2005** Conservatory of Recording Arts & Sciences, Tempe, AZ